http://www.centralcalswim.org/team/wzccslsc/page/about-ccs/privacy-policy

WELCOME to Central California Swimming!
Central California Swimming
CoachesSite Map
Sign in
HomeAbout CCSWhat is USA Swimming?Service AreaVision & Mission StatementsPrivacy PolicyCOPPA StatementProduct DeliveryRefund PolicyContact CCSDiversity and InclusionOutreach Membership DiscountMeetsLong Course 2020Short Course 2019-20Long Course 2019Short Course 2018-19Events PagePrevious Season ResultsSwimmer's LaneAll StarsZone TeamClub Achievement ProgramTime StandardsCCS Age Group RecordsThe Dry SideClubsAffliatesOfficersFormsGuidebookBy LawsAdministrationOfficer ReportsMinutesAwardsDirectionsRegistrationsBoard of Review / Appeals ProcessBy NameBy OfficeMembershipMeet SchedulingMeet Entry Time StandardsMeet Rules And RegulationsMeet Warm-Up ProcedureMeet Directors' ReportsOfficialsUse Of Colorado Timing SystemCode Of ConductChampionship And NationalAge Group Travel RequirementsCCS Records and AwardsUSAS ConventionName, Objectives, TerritoryMembershipDues and FeesHouse of DelegatesBoard of DirectorsOfficersDivisions, CommitteesAnnual Audit, ReportsMembers' Bill of RightsBoard of Review, HearingsOrganization, Amendment of BylawsIndemnificationParliamentary AuthorityPermanent Office and StaffMiscellaneousDefinitions, ConventionsAge GroupCoachesMembershipNational TravelOfficialsPropertySafetyTreasurerCoaches' CornerMembershipHy-Tek SupportIntroductionSafety CurriculumEducation RequiremntBackground ScreeningApplication ProcessAssistant CoachesInsurance DiscalimerOverviewCPRFirst AidSafety TrainingInstructorDisability WaiverIn MembershipAt MeetsAt PracticeOverviewDownload Meet ResultDownload Meet EventsExport Meet EventsMeet Entries ReportOn The DeckOfficials InfoSafetyOfficials' DocumentsOfficials AttireOfficials TrainingRecruitmentCCS Safety HandbookUSAS Safety RegsWinter SafetyPool LocationsDocumentsLinks
Central California Swimming (CCS) maintains a general audience website. The purpose of the website is to provide general information about the sport of swimming and specific information regarding the sport within our governance/service area. In addition, the website provides facilities for membership registration and competition entry.
CCS collects certain personal information necessary to register individuals as members, both athlete and non-athlete, of CCS and USA Swimming. That personal information is shared with USA Swimming as the parent organization of CCS. Additionally, personal information is shared with CCS member clubs to the extent necessary to conduct swimming competitions.
CCS collects certain credit card information necessary to complete monetary transactions for the collection of membership registration and competitive entry fees. That information is not saved or stored by CCS and is only shared with our credit card processor to authenticate ownership of the credit card and to verify availability of credit.
Cookies are used by the website solely to track data flow to and from the website. No information about any user's computer is retrieved.
Personal contact information is displayed on the website for the officers of CCS and for primary contacts of CCS member clubs. Athlete information is displayed in meet results and special recognition features of the website. The only personal information displayed is an athlete's name and age (not birthdate).
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by TeamUnify but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
© Copyright SportsEngine, Inc. This website is powered by GoMotion but is owned by and subject to the Organization’s privacy policy.
Privacy Statement
